(Leonard:)That's a biological impossibility,
and you didn't have to come.
Oh, yes. I could have stayed behind
to watch Wolowitz hit on Penny...
(Sheldon:)...in Russian, Arabic and Farsi.
And why can't she get her own TV?
(Leonard:)Come on, you know how it is
with breakups.
(Sheldon:)No, I don't, and neither do you.
But I... I broke up with Joyce Kim.
(Sheldon:)You did not break up with Joyce Kim.
She defected to North Korea.
(Leonard:)To mend her broken heart.
(Leonard:)This situation is much less complicated.
There's some dispute
between Penny and her ex-boyfriend...
(Leonard:)...as to who gets custody of the TV.
- She just wanted to avoid a scene with him.
- So we get to have a scene with him?
(Leonard:)No, Sheldon,
there's not going to be a scene.
(Leonard:)There's two of us and one of him.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, the two of us
can't even carry a TV.
(Penny(to Raj):)So you guys work with Leonard and Sheldon
at the university?
(Penny:)I'm sorry, do you speak English?